Daniel Shalem

Full-stack Developer

Gilboa, Israel

✓ dshctr1993@gmail.com



6 054-5882578

Full-Stack / Frontend Web Developer with knowledge and experience writing single-page-applications using the latest WEB technologies.

Team player, hard worker, focusing on problem solving and detailed orientation, self-learner responsible, and adapt quickly to new environments.

Check out my Latest project: Airbnb clone app, built with Vue3, Vuex, Nodejs MongoDB.

Skills

Programming Languages: Modern JavaScript (ES6), HTML5, CSS

Frameworks: React.js, Vue.js, Node.js, SCSS, Three js

Databases: MongoDB, MSSQL

State Management: Vuex, Redux

General knowledge: Object Oriented Programing, Design Patterns, PWA, SSR, Git-workflow

Work Experience

Full-Stack Developer / Hackyo



Oct 2022 - Current

Developed full-stack web application which processed, analyzed, and rendered data visually. Analyzed systems flow, data usage, and work processes.

Helped evolve front-end and back-end stack.

Director / Dor l'abait



Oct 2020 - May 2022

Director of a home care company for the elderly population.

As part of my work, I managed about 90 employees and provided service to hundreds of elderly residents of the city of Afula.



Education

Coding Academy



2022 - 2022

An intensive coding bootcamp (640 hours) that qualifies Full Stack developers.

University of Haifa



2020 - 2022

M.A Internaional Relations Specialization in negotiation and decision-making

Finished with excellence

The Max Stern Yezreel Valley College



2016-2019

B.S.W in Social work